const questions = [
    {
     question: "How many total commands are there for Indian Army?",
     options: ["3", "5", "10", "7"],
     correctAnswer: "7"
   },
   {
     question: "Indian Army Day is celebrated on which date?",
     options: ["13th March", "15th January", "15th August", "26th July"],
     correctAnswer: "15th January"
   },
   {
     question: "What is the motto of the Indian Navy?",
     options: ["Sham Nau Varunaha", "Sha-Nau-Varuna", "Sarve Santu Niramaya", "Jai Hind"],
     correctAnswer: "Sham Nau Varunaha"
   },
   {
     question: "Which Indian naval officer was awarded the Mahavir Chakra for his leadership during the Indo-Pakistani War of 1971?",
     options: ["Admiral Nirmal Kumar Verma", " Admiral Arun Prakash", "Admiral Sunil Lanba", "Commodore Babru Bhan Yadav"],
     correctAnswer: "Commodore Babru Bhan Yadav"
   },
   {
     question: "The commando unit of Indian Airforce is named as?",
     options: ["Marcos", "Garud", "Para", "Ghatak"],
     correctAnswer: "Garud"
   },
   {
     question: "The Paramilitary Forces in India operate under the administrative control of which ministry?",
     options: ["Ministry of Home Affairs", "Ministry of External Affairs", "Ministry of Finance", " Ministry of Defence"],
     correctAnswer: "Ministry of Home Affairs"
   },
   {
     question: "What is the primary role of the National Security Guard (NSG)?",
     options: ["Coastal Defence", "Border Security", "Air Defence", "Counter-terrorism"],
     correctAnswer: "Counter-terrorism"
   },
   {
     question: "Who is the first Chief of Defence Staff (CDS) of India?",
     options: ["General Bipin Rawat", "Air Chief Marshal R.K.S. Bhadauria", "General Manoj Mukund Naravane", "Admiral Karambir Singh"],
     correctAnswer: "General Bipin Rawat"
   },
   {
     question: "Which missile is an intercontinental ballistic missile (ICBM) developed by India?",
     options: ["Akash", "Prithvi", "BrahMos", "Agni-V"],
     correctAnswer: "Agni-V"
   },
   {
     question: "What is the name of the indigenously developed anti-satellite weapon system of India, successfully tested in 2019?",
     options: [" Operation Sagar Kavach", "Mission Shakti", "Project Valiant", "Operation Thunderbolt"],
     correctAnswer: "Mission Shakti"
   },
 ];
